born2impress.com 2009-04-28

# Privacy Policy

| Born 2 Impress does not disclose, share, exchange, sell or provide your information to any third party.  We treat your information with strict privacy and security and use it solely for the purposes for which it was initially collected.  
---  
**Information we collect**

We store the information you enter on our website when you fill out a form, send an e-mail, call our customer care center or enroll to participate in one of our offers or services. This information may include  

**We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or any other personal information via e-mail.**  
**Children's Privacy**

We are committed to protecting children's privacy on the Internet in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.  
  
**Security**

Our website uses Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) to encrypt your personal credit information before it is transmitted over the Internet. SSL technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions. Placing an order online at our website is just as safe as giving your credit card number over the phone.

Ela wrote this part about the **SECURITY.**  
  
**What are we doing there?**

Also, I want to make sure that the right click is not activated so people can’t copy any images or texts out of the site.  
  
**Your Consent**

By using our website, you consent to our use of information that is collected or submitted as described in this online privacy policy. We reserve the right edit/update this privacy policy so we encourage you to review it periodically. Please check the effective date at the bottom of the page to verify that you are familiar with our latest additions/deletions to our privacy policy.  
  
**Other Sites:**

Our website may contain external links to third party websites of vendors, individuals, partners or resource centers. Please note that this privacy policy applies only to the born2impress.com website. We are not responsible of websites you may navigate.  Please refer to their privacy policy to verify their security practices.

Enjoy your confidential, secure shopping experience at Born 2 Impress!
